

## **My Contact**

atifsalehin731@gmail.com

**(** +8801744187326

229,Moghbazar-Noyatola, Dhaka-1217

## **Hard Skill**

- Social Media Managing
- Voiceover Artist
- Data Entry & processing
- Copywriting
- · Article Writing
- Data mining and analysis
- Social Media Marketing
- Sales/Idea Management
- Communication
- Basic Computer skills (MS word/PowerPoint/Excel)

#### **Soft Skill**

- Observation
- · Decision making
- Development generate
- Multi-tasking

## **Education Background**

National Bank Public School

Secondary School Certificate Completed in 2018 G.P.A. 5.00

Government Science College

Higher Secondary School Certificate Completed 2020 G.P.A. 5.00

University of Asia Pacific

Bachelor of Science in Computer Science & Engineering From 2022 - Present G.P.A. so far 3.53

## **Achievements**

2022 - **Winner of Quiz Competition** Software and Hardware Club

2023 - **Ist Runner up of Idea Season 2.**Entrepreneurship and Career
Development Club

# Md. Atif Salehin

## **DIGITAL MARKETER**

## **About Me**

Atif Salehin

I'm a highly skilled and educated graphic and user experience designer who brings a wealth of experience and expertise to the field. With a strong background in Social Media Management, I've successfully designed for various platforms and always taking immense pride in the quality of work delivered. I'm an individual with unwavering enthusiasm and self-motivation and is known for being reliable, responsible, and exceptionally hardworking. Demonstrating maturity and adaptability, i like to thrive in challenging situations, excelling both as a team player and an independent contributor. Moreover, I've always had my work done under pressure, consistently meeting and surpassing strict deadlines with a focused and dedicated approach.

## **Professional Experience**

Junior Social media Designer And Social Media Manager at Dana n Decor

2019 - 2021

Key responsibilities:

- · Analyzing engagement data.
- Social media marketing.
- Product Idea designing.
- Identifying trends in customer interactions and planning digital campaigns to build community online.
- Working with marketing professionals to develop social media marketing campaigns.

#### Information Analysis and Data Entry Executive at Echithi

2022 - Present

- Preparing and sorting documents for data entry.
- Entering data into database software and checking to ensure the accuracy of the data that has been inputted.
- Resolving discrepancies in information and obtaining further information for incomplete documents.
- Creating data backups as part of a contingency plan.

#### **Professional Voiceover Artist**

2023 - Present

- · Versatile Vocal Range
- Exceptional Articulation
- Emotional Resonance
- Adaptability to Scripts
- Professionalism and Reliability

## Volunteer experience

- ICPC World Finals, Dhaka, 2022
- Brake The Barriers, Workshop 2023
- VOLUNTEER, Directorate of Students' Welfare

# **My Reference**

Zaforullah Momtaz

Echithi / General Manager +8801723722788 **Abrar Al Rawnak** 

Dana N Decor / CEO +46732441395